https://www.pcprofessor.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Covid-19 Update: All classes meeting online, as scheduled.
HOMEUPCOMING ZOOM CLASS SCHEDULECLASSES Academic FinancingApplication Classes Access DatabaseClass Manuals and FilesClass SyllabusExcel SpreadsheetsMicrosoft OutlookMicrosoft WordQuickbooksWindows BeginnerCisco Router TrainingComputer Maintenance Technology (CMT)Computer Repair ClassEthical Hacker & ForensicsMicrosoft MCSE PreparatoryOur ClassroomsWeb Design ClassSERVICES Billpay & Prepaid Services Prepaid Service/Training HoursPay a PC Professor InvoiceClassroom RentalComputer Repair ServicesCorporate SeminarsHire a PC Professor StudentIT Training ClassesOnsite Testing Center Pearson Test SchedulingCertiport Test SchedulingAuthorized Mensa Testing CenterPrivate TutoringSchool Gift and Bookstore PC Professor Gift & BookstorePrepaid Service HoursLow Cost InternetTuition Gift CertificatesHotel Discounts Hilton Partner DiscountHampton Inn DiscountTestimonialsTuition FinancingWeb Design & ProgrammingSTUDENTS Employment Assistance Hire a PC Professor StudentPlacement AssistanceFrequent Hire Club“I Got A Job!” NotificationEmployment Verification FormPersonal Work PlanEducational Tax CreditsFive Minute FinancingForms and Uploads ACH UpdateDiploma RequestDiploma UploadTranscript RequestWeb Hosting RequestLabs & eLearning Portal Classroom Learning LabsInstructor AccessRemote Classroom AccessSatisfaction SurveySoftware Downloads Microsoft Academic SoftwareVMware SoftwareStudent CatalogIn The NewsSCHOLARSHIPS Start HERE for Grant, Scholarship & Financing Opportunities!5 Minute Financing ApplicationAmerican Indian Career GrantAmerican Military Veterans GrantCorporate Job Growth GrantIn Jacob’s Shoes For YouthLewis Bass ScholarshipSSI-SSDI Training GrantTourette Syndrome ScholarshipUnemployed/Displaced WorkerCONTACT Arrange a Consultation, Meeting, School Tour or Service CallContact Us
Privacy Policyadmin72019-09-19T23:15:35-04:00
PC Professor Technical Institute
Privacy Policy of https://www.PCProfessor.Edu
Privacy Policy
Effective date: September 20, 2019
PC Professor (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.PCProfessor.Edu website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve our Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.PCProfessor.Edu
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes so that we may provide and continuously improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, a referral source, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
As do most modern websites, we may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent and still be able to participate in our Service.
Examples of Cookies we may use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
PC Professor uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To track placement of our Students
To effectively communicate with our Students and prospective Students
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
To uphold contractual obligations to Federal, State, Local, Non-Profit and/or Private scholarship sponsors
To track and store data and statistics needed for annual data reporting, required of all licensed Florida schools
To properly schedule Students in the proper classes at the proper times at the proper campus
By providing us with your contact data, you are requesting and opting-in to contact via email, text, mailing or telephone, even if your name appears on a State and/or Federal Do Not Call Registry.
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we may transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States where is is processed on our servers.  As of September 20, 2019, these servers are located in Arizona.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
PC Professor may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of PC Professor
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  Please do not submit any confidential, private or classified information through our website.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties may have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf.
Analytics
We may use third-party products and providers similar to and/or including Google Analytics to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.  This helps us help you.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you may be directed to a third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service is not targeted towards those under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children or Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If you become aware that we may have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, please let us know so that we may take steps to remove that information from our servers.
GDPR and the CCPA
The General Data Protection Regulation was adopted on April 14, 2016, and became enforceable on May 25, 2018.
The State of California passed the California Consumer Privacy Act on June 28, 2018, taking effect on January 1, 2020.  It grants rights to transparency and control over the collection of personal information by companies in a similar means to GDPR.  As a Florida licensed school, PC Professor does not target nor does it intentionally collect information from California residents.
As a non-EU establishment, PC Professor is exempt from GDPR and designating an EU Representative when the processing is only occasional and does not include, on a large scale, processing of special categories of data as referred to in Article 9(1) GDPR or processing of personal data relating to criminal convictions and offences referred to in Article 10 GDPR, and such processing is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons, taking into account the nature, context, scope and purposes of the processing.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
In such cases, we may update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By visiting the contact page on our website:  https://www.pcprofessor.com/pc-professor-contact-us
5 Minute Financing
Grant Eligibility Assessment Form
Unemployed Worker Grant
Transcript Request
Onsite Testing Center
American Military Veterans
American Indian Vocational
Web Design and SEO Services
W3C-WAI Friendly
WAIT! PLEASE INTRODUCE YOURSELF:
Thousands of successful graduates!
SESSIONS BEGIN WEEKLY!
Unlimited Phone Support!
SMALL, HANDS-ON CLASSES!
Complimentary Audit Courses!
JOB PLACEMENT ASSISTANCE!
Grants and scholarships may be available to those who qualify!
*SUBMIT*
×
Do you want massive traffic?
Scelerisque augue ac hac, aliquet, nascetur turpis. Augue diam phasellus odio lorem integer, aliquam aliquam sociis nisi adipiscing hacac.
Goblinus globalus fantumo tubus dia
Scelerisque cursus dignissim lopatico
Montes vutario lacus quis preambul
Leftomato denitro oculus softam lorum
Spiratio dodenus christmas gulleria tix
Dualo fitemus lacus quis preambul bela
PGlmcmFtZSB3aWR0aD0iMTAwJSIgaGVpZ2h0PSIxMDAlIiBzcmM9Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnlvdXR1YmUuY29tL2VtYmVkL2o4bFNjSE8ybU0wIiBmcmFtZWJvcmRlcj0iMCIgYWxsb3dmdWxsc2NyZWVuPjwvaWZyYW1lPg==
* we never share your details with third parties.
×
Get Instant Access
ARE YOU READY? GET IT NOW!
Increase more than 500% of Email Subscribers!
Your Information will never be shared with any third party.
SUBSCRIBE NOW!
×
